Alan Rafkin Papers
Alan Rafkin Papers
1970-1994
Rafkin, Alan, 1928-2001.
22 linear ft.
Alan Rafkin was an American television producer and director, primarily of situation comedies. Collection includes television scripts (ca. 750), videocassettes (ca. 200), and memorabilia.
149707
Biographical History
Alan Rafkin is an alumnus of Syracuse University and one of the most talented directors of television sitcoms. His career, spanning over forty years, has included such shows as The Andy Griffith Show, The Dick Van Dyke Show, M*A*S*H, Coach and Suddenly Susan among many others. Rafkin won an Emmy Award in 1982 for directing One Day at a Time and in 1998 he wrote his autobiography entitled, Cue The Bunny On The Rainbow: Tales From TV's Most Prolific Sitcom Director.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Alan Rafkin Papers is divided into scripts, videos and memorabilia. Scripts contains more than 700 scripts from television shows, mostly situation comedies; shows represented include Alice, The Bob Newhart Show, Charles in Charge, Coach, The Governor and J.J., It's Gary Shandling's Show, Laverne and Shirley, Love American Style, The Love Boat, Me & the Chimp, One Day At a Time, Sanford and Son, and Viva Valdez. Videos contains nearly 200 recordings of television shows, most of which are those represented in the scripts series. Videotapes are in one of three formats: VHS, Beta, U-matic. The format for each tape is given in parenthesis. Memorabilia comprises 2 boxes of miscellaneous memorabilia.
Arrangement of the Collection
Scripts and Videos are arranged alphabetically by title and within that in order by catalog number. Memorabilia is unprocessed and remains as received by.
Related Material
has a number of television-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Rafkin, Alan, 1928-2001.; Television -- Production and direction.; Television broadcasting.; Television broadcasting -- Auditions.; Television broadcasting -- Awards.; Television comedies.; Television pilot programs.; Television plays.; Television producers and directors -- United States.; Television scripts.; Television series -- United States.; Television specials.; Videotapes.; Betacam (TM); VHS.; Memorabilia.; Television scripts.; Producers and directors.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Alan Rafkin, 1994.
Inventory
- Scripts
  - ABC Movie Of the Week
    - 42109 Let's Switch (Box 1)
  - Act Your Age
    - [no number] (Box 1)
  - Alice
    - 166566 Mel's In Love (Box 1)
    - 166567 The Accident (Box 1)
    - 166569 The Hex (Box 1)
    - 166572 A Night To Remember (Box 1)
    - [no number] The Failure (Box 1)
    - [no number] Pain of No Return (Box 1)
  - The Andy Griffith Show
    - 12H(231) Andy's Investment (Box 1)
  - An Angel in My Pocket
    - 02021 (Box 1)
  - Anne in Blue
    - [no number] (Pilot) (Box 1)
  - Another April
    - [no number] (Box 1)
  - Arnie
    - [no number] Second Honeymoon (Box 1)
  - The Astonishing Crime of Herkimer E. Saticoy
    - [no number] (Box 1)
  - The Bandit
    - 01988 (Box 1)
  - Blansky's Beauties
    - 60881-007 Nancy Meets Francis (Box 1)
    - 60881-011 To Nancy With Love (Box 1)
    - 60881-012 Dear Nancy... (Box 1)
    - 60881-013 Nancy Breaks a Leg (Box 1)
  - The Bob Newhart Show
    - 4055 Jerry Robinson Crusoe (Box 1)
    - 4062 Brutally Yours Bob Hartley (Box 1)
    - 4065 Home Is Where the Hurt Is (Box 1)
    - 4066 Ship Of Shrinks (Box 1)
    - 4071 Serve For Daylight (Box 1)
    - 4074 A Pound Of Flesh (Box 1)
    - 4076 The Ceiling Hits Bob (Box 1)
    - 7266 Not With My Sister You Don't (Box 1)
    - 7451 The Battle of the Groups (Box 1)
    - 7453 My Business Is Shrinking (Box 1)
    - 7459 Dr. Ryan's Express (Box 1)
  - The Boys
    - [no number] no title (Box 1)
    - 101 no title (Box 1)
    - 102 Some Don't Like It Hot (Box 1)
    - 103 The Apartment (Box 1)
    - 104 The Woman Who Came To Dinner (Box 1)
    - 107 The Asians Are Coming (Box 1)
  - Breezin'
    - [no number] (Pilot) (Box 1)
  - Camperbaggers
    - proposal (Box 1)
  - Charles in Charge
    - 59303 Cousin Elliot (Box 1)
    - 59307 Discipline (Box 1)
    - 59308 Friends and Lovers (Box 1)
    - 59310 Slumber Party (Box 1)
    - 59316 Trick Or Treat (Box 1)
    - 59318 The Awakening (Box 1)
    - 59319 Home For the Holidays (Box 1)
    - 59324 Accidental Puppy (Box 1)
    - 59325 The Commotion (Box 1)
    - 59326 Mr. Brilliant (Box 1)
    - 59327 Pressure From Grandma (Box 2)
    - 59328 Mr. President (Box 2)
    - 59329 Jill's Decision (Box 2)
    - 59330 Snowbound (Box 2)
    - 59331 Charles 'R' Us (Box 2)
    - 59332 The Last Resort (Box 2)
    - 59333 The Wrong Guy (Box 2)
    - 59334 Meet Grampa (Box 2)
    - 95827 no title (Box 2)
  - Charlie & Company
    - 6S04 Who's Watching the Roads (Box 2)
    - 6S05 The World According To Jim (Box 2)
    - 6S06 Like Father Like Son (Box 2)
    - 6S07 Will Be Around (Box 2)
    - 6S08 Operation Richmond (Box 2)
    - 6S09 Happy Anniversary...Sort Of (Box 2)
    - 6S11 Beaus and Arrows (Box 2)
    - 6S12 Silent Knight (Box 2)
    - 6S13 Rent and Rave (Box 2)
    - 6S14 Here's Rachel (Box 2)
    - 6S15 Don't Take My Son... Please (Box 2)
    - 6S16 When You Least Expect it (Box 2)
    - 6S17 Rachel and the Stranger (Box 2)
    - 6S79 no title (Pilot) (Box 2)
    - 0101 Easy For You To Say (Box 2)
    - 0102 Buddy Can You Spare My Dime? (Box 2)
  - Chicken Soup
    - 102 The Reservation (Box 2)
    - 103 The Dinner (Box 2)
    - 104 The Bartender (Box 2)
    - 105 Double Date (Box 2)
    - 106 Take My Kids...Please (Box 2)
    - 107 Bea Moves Out (Box 2)
    - 108 The Ralph Hearns Story (Box 2)
    - 109 Operation Jackie (Box 2)
    - 110 Almost Father Jackie (Box 2)
    - 111 Bea's Night Out (Box 2)
    - 112 Community Service (Box 2)
  - Coach
    - 65511 Coaches Conference (Box 2)
    - 65515 The Curley O'Brien Award (Box 2)
    - 65521 Kelly Girl (Box 2)
    - 66601 That Shouldn't Happen (Box 2)
    - 66602 Is This Your First time On the Riverboat Miss Watkins (Box 2)
    - 66604 The Day That Moses Came to Town (Box 2)
    - 66606 Magnificent Abcession (Box 2)
    - 66607 The Marion Kind part 1 (Box 2)
    - 66608 The Marion Kind part 2 (Box 2)
    - 66609 Hayden and Luther's Excellent Adventure (Box 2)
    - 66610 Hayden's In The Kitchen With Dinah (Box 2)
    - 66611 The Break Up (Box 2)
    - 66612 The Iceman Goeth (Box 2)
    - 66613 Cabin Fever (Box 2)
    - 66614 Men Don't Heal (Box 2)
    - 66615 When Hayden Met Christine (Box 2)
    - 66616 Four Rosebrocks Three Coaches Two Foxes and an Armstrong (Box 2)
    - 66617 Puppy Love (Box 3)
    - 66618 Dauber Graduates (Box 3)
    - 66622 Hurly-Burleigh (Box 3)
    - 66623 Hayden Fox For Universal Jocks (Box 3)
    - 66624 The Father and Son Reunion (Box 3)
    - 66625 Diamonds Are a Dentist's Best Friend (Box 3)
    - 67201 The Kick-Off & The Kiss-Off (Box 3)
    - 67202 Since My Beaver Left Me (Box 3)
    - 67203 Don't Get Mad Get Cooley (Box 3)
    - 67205 Any Place I Hang Myself Is Home (Box 3)
    - 67206 I Think I Can't I Think I Can't (Box 3)
    - 67208 A Real Guy's Guy (Box 3)
    - 67209 Dateline: Bangkok (Box 3)
    - 67210 Loonstruck (Box 3)
    - 67211 Requiem For a Groundskeeper (Box 3)
    - 67212 Pineapple Bowl part 1 (Box 3)
    - 67213 Pineapple Bowl part 2 (Box 3)
    - 67214 Rizendough Revisited (Box 3)
    - 67215 I Hate Barbara (Box 3)
    - 67216 Return Of the Marriage Killer (Box 3)
    - 67217 The War Of the Dopes (Box 3)
    - 67219 No Good Deed Goes Unpunished (Box 3)
    - 67220 Last Of the Red Hot Luthers (Box 3)
    - 67222 The Old Fish and the Shoes (Box 3)
    - 67223 If That's Opportunity Don't Answer (Box 3)
    - 67224 Frequent Flyers Crossed Wires (Box 3)
    - 67225 Can we Go Home Now (Box 3)
    - 68301 To Air Is Human (Box 3)
    - 68302 Love Me Tender (Box 3)
    - 68303 Born Luther (Box 3)
    - 68307 Dirty Tricks (Box 3)
    - 68309 The Bachelor Party (Box 3)
    - 68310 Father Of the Year (Box 3)
    - 68311 Rizzendough Rendezvous (Box 3)
    - 68312 Vows (Box 3)
    - 68313 The Patriot Bowl (Box 3)
    - 68316 The Commercial part 1 (Box 3)
    - 68317 The Commercial part 2 (Box 3)
    - 68318 Vegas Odds (Box 3)
    - 68319 Buzzy Money (Box 3)
    - 68320 The Bigger They Are (Box 3)
    - 68321 Luthario (Box 3)
    - 68323 Why So Happy Hayden (Box 3)
    - 68324 One For the Road (Box 3)
    - 69201 Baby. On Board (Box 3)
    - 69202 Nice Work If You Can Get IT (Box 3)
    - 69203 Belly of the Beast (Box 3)
    - 69204 The Luck Stops Here (Box 3)
    - 69205 If She Can Make It There... (Box 3)
    - 69206 Running On Empty (Box 3)
    - 69208 It Came From New York (Box 3)
    - 69210 The Pioneer Bowl (Box 3)
    - 69213 The Sand-In (Box 3)
    - 69216 The Playbook (Box 3)
    - 69217 The Devil In Mrs. Burleigh (Box 3)
    - 69218 Babywreckers (Box 3)
    - 69219 Like Father Like Daughter (Box 3)
    - 69224 Blue Chip Blues (Box 3)
    - 69225 Something Old Something New (Box 3)
    - 69226 One of the Guys (Box 3)
    - 69227 My Best Friend's Girl (Box 3)
    - 69809 Kicker, The (Box 3A)
    - 69814 Luther and Ruthanne Take the Big 12 Steps (Box 3A)
    - 69816 My Fair Agent (Box 3A)
    - 69817 Did Someone Call Me Snorer (Box 3A)
    - K0306 Bo Knows (Box 3A)
    - K0322 Save the Wave (Box 3A)
    - KO328 Luther, Get Your Gun (Box 3A)
    - 82144 One Hour Special (Box 3)
  - The Cop and the Kid
    - 60781-009 Not With My Teacher (Box 4)
    - 60781-010 Previous Engagement (Box 4)
  - The Courtship of Eddie's Father
    - [no number] Mrs. Livingston -- I Presume? (Box 4)
  - Daddy's Girl
    - 3900-P Flossie and Religion (Box 4)
  - A Family for Joe
    - 105600 Life of the Party (Box 4)
    - 106600 Nick's Heart (Box 4)
    - 107600 Having a Baby (Box 4)
    - 108600 Night School (Box 4)
  - Father John and Mister O'Connor
    - proposal (Box 4)
  - The Flim-Flam Man
    - [no number] no title (Box 4)
  - The Friday Night Group
    - 183071 no title (Box 4)
  - Friends & Lovers
    - 4203 The Groupie (Box 4)
    - 4204 Design For Living (Box 4)
    - 4207 All's Well That Ends (Box 4)
    - 4208 Fiddler In the House (Box 4)
  - Get Smart
    - 1645-0956 Smart Fell On Alabama (Box 4)
    - 1645-0958 Ice Station Siegfried (Box 4)
    - 1645-0971 Do I Hear a Vaults? (Box 4)
  - The Ghost Writer
    - B89010 A Comedy of Terrors (Box 4)
  - Glitter
    - GL-001 On Your Toes (Box 4)
    - GL-003 The Tribute (Box 4)
  - Good Advice
    - 205 Two Times Twenty (Box 4)
  - The Good Guys
    - 0810 To Catch a Rufus (Box 4)
  - The Governor and J.J.
    - 1646-0655 Rhyme With Reasons (Box 4)
    - 1646-0663 Bunky's Buddy (Box 4)
    - 1646-0664 Never Judge a Book By Its Naked Cover (Box 4)
    - 1646-0665 Once Upon a War (Box 4)
    - 1646-0666 The Last Weekend (Box 4)
    - 1646-0667 The Tic-Toc Tale (Box 4)
    - 1646-0672 The Return Of Doctor Livingston (Box 4)
    - 1646-0675 Second Opinion (Box 4)
    - 1646-0901 Run Ballerina Run (Box 4)
    - 1646-0902 And the Word Begat the Bleep (Box 4)
    - 1646-0903 Read That Leg To Me Again (Box 4)
    - 1646-0904 Ben and Her (Box 4)
    - 1646-0908 Check the Check (Box 4)
    - 1646-0909 Fawcett Is Running (Box 4)
    - 1646-0911 Twice In a Lifetime (Box 4)
    - 1646-0912 A Day In the Life... (Box 4)
  - Hanging In
    - 0101 New Man On Campus (Box 4)
    - 0102 Old Girlfriend (Box 4)
    - 0103 Lou's Little Problem (Box 4)
  - Hello Larry
    - 0101A How To Not To (Box 4)
  - Hope & Gloria
    - 456957 My Mama Done Told Me (Box 3A)
    - 456959 Love With an Improper Stranger (Box 3A)
    - 456960 Face With Two Men, The (Box 3A)
    - 457763 Enemies, A Love Story (Box 3A)
    - 457764 Danny, Oh Boy (Box 3A)
    - 457765 Tainted Love (Box 3A)
    - 457766 One Sorry Mother (Box 3A)
    - 457772 Note to Self (Box 3A)
    - Miscellaneous, production schedules, cast and crew list (Box 3A)
  - How to Frame a Figg
    - 2040 (Box 4)
  - It's Gary Shandling's Show
    - SHAN102 Grant Gets Broken (Box 4)
    - SHAN104 Foul Ball (Box 4)
    - SHAN105 The Graduate (Box 4)
    - SHAN106 It's Garry's Problem but It's Jojo's Show (Box 4)
    - SHAN107 Garry Met a Girl Named Maria (Box 4)
    - SHAN109 Fate (Box 4)
    - SHAN110 Grant's Date (Box 4)
    - SHAN111 no title (Box 5)
    - SHAN112 The Morning After (Box 5)
    - SHAN113 Laffie (Box 5)
    - SHAN114 Dial "L" For Laundry (Box 5)
    - SHAN115 Dinner With Garry (Box 5)
    - SHAN116 Force Boxman (Box 5)
    - SHAN201 Who's Poppa (Box 5)
    - SHAN202 No Baby No Show (Box 5)
    - SHAN203 The Fugitive (Box 5)
    - SHAN205 The Schumakers Go To Hollywood (Box 5)
    - SHAN206 Killer Routine (Box 5)
    - SHAN207 Angelica part 1 (Box 5)
    - SHAN208 Angelica part 2 (Box 5)
    - SHAN209 It's Garry Shandling's Christmas Show (Box 5)
    - SHAN210 Mr. Sparks (Box 5)
    - SHAN212 Our Town (Box 5)
    - SHAN213 Save the Planet (Box 5)
    - SHAN214 The Grant Shuffle (Box 5)
    - SHAN215 Go Go Goldblum (Box 5)
    - SHAN216 Garry Falls down a Hole (Box 5)
    - SHAN217 Mr. Smith Goes to Nam (Box 5)
    - SHAN301 Goin' Places (Box 5)
    - SHAN302 Pete's Got a Secret (Box 5)
    - SHAN303 What's Happening To Me (Box 5)
    - SHAN304 Ruth's Place (Box 5)
    - SHAN305 The Natural (Box 5)
    - SHAN306 The Election Show (Box 5)
    - SHAN307 Vegas part 1 (Box 5)
    - SHAN308 Vegas part 2 (Box 5)
    - SHAN309 Home Sweet Home (Box 5)
    - SHAN310 Save Mr. Peck's part 1 (Box 5)
    - SHAN311 Save Mr. Peck's part 2 (Box 5)
    - SHAN313 Garry Acts Like a Moron (Box 5)
    - SHAN314 Kramer vs. Grant (Box 5)
    - SHAN317 Going Going Gone (Box 5)
  - Jeff Foxworthy Show, The
    - 101 Jeff's Life (Pilot) (Box 3A)
    - 102 Non-Affair to Remember (Box 3A)
    - 103 Gene Pool, The (Box 3A)
    - 106 With Two You Get Cow's Milk (Box 3A)
    - 107 Jeff & Ray & Rascal's Big Adventure (Final Script and Rough Draft) (Box 3A)
    - 108 Sore Winner, A (Box 3A)
    - 109 He's Making a List, Checking it Twice (Box 3A)
    - 110 Foxworthy Family Feud (Box 3A)
    - 111 Matt About You (Box 3A)
  - Jesse
    - 225758 Leggo My Diego (Box 3A)
    - Cast and crew list (Box 3A)
  - Joe's World
    - 0101 The Initiation (Box 5)
  - Just You and Me
    - 0732-0106 Frank's Date (Box 5)
  - Laverne and Shirley
    - 60793-039 Take my Plants - Please! (Box 5)
    - 60793-040 An Affair to Forget part 1 (Box 5)
    - 60793-041 An Affair to Forget part 2 (Box 5)
    - 60793-042 Airport '59 (Box 5)
    - 60793-043 Tag Team Wrestling (Box 5)
    - 60793-044 The Pact (Box 5)
    - 60793-045 The Robot Lawsuit (Box 5)
    - 60793-046 Laverne and Shirley meet Fabian (Box 5)
    - 60793-047 Laverne's Arranged Marriage (Box 5)
    - 60793-048 Shirley's Operation (Box 5)
    - 60793-049 The Stakeout (Box 5)
    - 60793-050 The Morticians (Box 5)
    - 60793-051 The Slow Child (Box 5)
    - 60793-052 New Year's Eve - 1960 (Box 5)
    - 60793-053 The Horse Show (Box 5)
    - 60793-054 The Dentist (Box 5)
    - 60793-056 The Bus Stop (Box 5)
    - 60793-057 The Driving Test (Box 5)
    - 60793-058 The Obstacle Course (Box 5)
    - 60793-062 Breakin' Up and Makin' Up (Box 5)
  - Legs
    - 60182-004 The Odd Family (Pilot) (Box 5)
  - Lily
    - [no number] no title (Box 5)
  - Liz
    - 0311-02020738TG no title (Pilot) (Box 5)
  - Local 306
    - [no number] no title (Box 6)
  - Lotsa Luck
    - 2628-17 A Little Order of Law and Order (Box 6)
    - 2628-18 You Oughta Be in Pictures (Box 6)
    - 2628-19 Stan's Assistant (Box 6)
    - 2628-21 Bummy's Girl (Box 6)
  - Love American Style
    - 60323-101 Hour One
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Motel Mixup (Box 6)
      - Love and the Anniversary Divorce (Box 6)
      - Love and the Doctor's Husband (Box 6)
    - 60323-102 Hour Two
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Conjugal Visit (Box 6)
      - Love and the Sweet Sixteen (Box 6)
      - Love and the Bashful Groom (Box 6)
      - Love and the Dream Burglar (Box 6)
      - Love and the Ledge (Box 6)
    - 60323-103 Hour Three
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Monsters (Box 6)
      - Love and the Scroungers (Box 6)
      - Love and the Old Cowboy (Box 6)
    - 60323-104 Hour Four
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Vacation (Box 6)
      - Love and the Advice Column (Box 6)
      - Love and the Plumber (Box 6)
      - Love and the Well Groomed Bride (Box 6)
    - 60323-105 Hour Five
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Married Bachelor (Box 6)
      - Love and Formula 26B (Box 6)
      - Love and the Hotel Caper (Box 6)
      - Love and the Reincarnation (Box 6)
    - 60323-106 Hour Six
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Penal Code (Box 6)
      - Love and the Mistress (Box 6)
      - Love and the Lovesick Sailor (Box 6)
      - Love and the Ski Lodge (Box 6)
    - 60323-107 Hour Seven
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Loud-Mouth (Box 6)
      - Love and the Sex Survey (Box 6)
      - Love and the Test of Manhood (Box 6)
      - Love and the Baby (Box 6)
      - Love and the New Size 8 (Box 6)
    - 60323-108 Hour Eight
      - Love and the Artful Codger (Box 6)
      - Love and the Plane Truth (Box 6)
      - Love and the Neglected Wife (Box 6)
      - Love and the Travelling Salesman (Box 6)
    - 60323-109 Hour Nine
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Free Weekend (Box 6)
      - Love and the Waitress (Box 6)
      - Love and the Guilty Conscience (Box 6)
      - Love and the Jealous Husband (Box 6)
      - Love and the Small Wedding (Box 6)
    - 60323-110 Hour Ten
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Television Weekend (Box 6)
      - Love and the Tuba (Box 6)
      - Love and the Water Bed (Box 6)
      - Love and the See-Through Man (Box 6)
    - 60323-111 Hour Eleven
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Wake-Up Girl (Box 6)
      - Love and the Intruder (Box 6)
      - Love and the Mixed Marriage (Box 6)
      - Love and the Detective (Box 6)
      - Love and the Lady Barber (Box 6)
    - 60323-112 Hour Twelve
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Four-Sided Triangle (Box 6)
      - Love and the Big Mother (Box 6)
      - Love and the Awakening (Box 6)
      - Love and the Naked Stranger (Box 6)
    - 60323-113 Hour Thirteen
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Eyewitnesses (Box 6)
      - Love and the Long Black Limousine (Box 6)
      - Love and the Contact Lens (Box 6)
      - Love and the Hiccups (Box 6)
      - Love and the Particular Girl (Box 6)
      - Love and the Physical (Box 6)
    - 60323-114 Hour Fourteen
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the College Professor (Box 6)
      - Love and the Accidental Passion (Box 6)
      - Love and the Bowling Ball (Box 6)
      - Love and the Eskimo's Wife (Box 6)
    - 60323-115 Hour Fifteen
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Liberated Lady Boss (Box 6)
      - Love and the Lover's Lane (Box 6)
      - Love and the House Bachelor (Box 6)
      - Love and the Fountain of Youth (Box 6)
    - 60323-116 Hour Sixteen
      - Production records (Box 6)
      - Love and the Check (Box 7)
      - Love and the Lovely Evening (Box 7)
      - Love and the Single Sisters (Box 7)
      - Love and the Bachelor Party (Box 7)
      - Love and the Latin Lover (Box 7)
    - 60323-117 Hour Seventeen
      - Production records (Box 7)
      - Love and the Fullback (Box 7)
      - Love and the Bathtub (Box 7)
      - Love and the Lady Athlete (Box 7)
      - Love and the Instant Father (Box 7)
      - Love and the Big Surprise (Box 7)
      - Love and the Lady Killers (Box 7)
    - 60323-118 Hour Eighteen
      - Production records (Box 7)
      - Love and the Guru (Box 7)
      - Love and the Boomerang (Box 7)
      - Love and the Anxious Mama (Box 7)
      - Love and the Alibi (Box 7)
      - Love and the Security Building (Box 7)
      - Love and the Topless Policy (Box 7)
    - 60323-947 Blackouts
      - [no number] (Box 7)
      - Love and Mother (Box 7)
      - Love and Unmarriage (Box 7)
      - Love and the Athlete (Box 7)
      - Love and the Doormat (Box 7)
      - Love and the Duel (Box 7)
      - Love and the Letter (Box 7)
      - Love and the Militant (Box 7)
      - Love and the Modern Wife (Box 7)
      - Love and the Salesman (Box 7)
      - Love and the Split-Up (Box 7)
      - Love and the Unhappy Couple (Box 7)
      - Love and the Young Unmarrieds (Box 7)
    - Casting records (Box 7)
  - The Love Boat
    - K-32
      - Folks From Home (Box 7)
      - The Captain's Cup (Box 7)
      - Legal Eagle (Box 7)
    - K-50
      - The Affair (Box 7)
      - Eleanor's Return (Box 7)
      - Not Now I'm Dying (Box 7)
    - K-51
      - no title (Box 7)
    - K-52
      - One Rose a Day (Box 7)
      - Gopher's Greatest Hit (Box 7)
      - The Vacation (Box 7)
    - K-53
      - Going My Way? (Box 7)
      - Dance With Me (Box 7)
      - The Proverb (Box 7)
    - K-71
      - First Time out (Box 7)
    - K-72
      - Graham and Kelly (Box 7)
    - K-73
      - "Ex" Plus "Y" (Box 7)
    - K-74
      - One If By Land (Box 7)
    - K-75
      - Oh Dale! (Box 7)
    - T-30
      - Isaac's Aegean Affair (Box 7)
      - The Captain and the Kid (Box 7)
      - Poor Rich Man (Box 7)
      - The Dean and the Flunker (Box 7)
  - The Mary Tyler Moore Show
    - 7002 Support Your Local Mother (Box 7)
    - 7008 Keep Your Guard Up (Box 7)
    - 7011 Divorce Isn't Everything (Box 7)
    - 7409 What Are Friends For (Box 7)
  - M*A*S*H
    - U-853 Lt. Radar O'Reilly (Box 7)
    - U-868 The General's Practitioner (Box 7)
  - Me & the Chimp
    - 60371-001 My Pet the Thief (Box 7)
    - 60371-002 Mike's Day With Buttons (Box 7)
    - 60371-003 Mike The Matchmaker (Box 7)
    - 60371-004 One Romantic Evening (Box 7)
    - 60371-005 Tennis Anyone? (Box 7)
    - 60371-006 Mike's Burglar Alarm (Box 8)
    - 60371-007 Mike's Big Act (Box 8)
    - 60371-008 The Lost Flashlight (Box 8)
    - 60371-009 The Paint Job (Box 8)
    - 60371-010 The Ghost Town (Box 8)
    - 60371-011 Mike's Night In (Box 8)
    - 60371-012 Hoop-Lah (Box 8)
    - 60371-013 Liz's Allergy (Box 8)
    - [no number] Baseball Ala Ape (Box 8)
    - [no number] Buttons Goes To the Shrink (Box 8)
    - [no number] Love Is a Many Splintered Thing (Box 8)
    - [no number] Mike and the Space Hero (Box 8)
    - [no number] Mike's Allergy (Box 8)
    - [no number] The Mutt- story proposal (Box 8)
    - [no number] The Neilson Rating - story proposal (Box 8)
  - The Michelle Lee Show
    - [no number] no title (Box 8)
  - Murphy Brown
    - 455917 The Anchorman (Box 8)
    - 455925 ...The More They Stay the Same (Box 8)
    - 456159 Prelude to a Kiss (Box 8)
    - Staff and crew list (Box 8)
  - Nancy
    - 4400 Guess Who's Coming To the White House (Box 8)
    - 4402 Adam the TV Star (Box 8)
    - 4405 Going Going Gone (Box 8)
  - The Nancy Walker Show
    - 0106 The Anniversary part 1 (Box 8)
    - 0107 The Anniversary part 2 (Box 8)
    - 0108 Terry's Depression (Box 8)
    - 0109 Rival Agents (Box 8)
    - 0110 Lorraine's Career (Box 8)
    - 0111 Dear Dr. Dora (Box 8)
    - 0112 The Partners (Box 8)
    - 0113 The Reunion (Box 8)
    - [no number] Debbie of the Derby (Box 8)
  - The Odd Couple
    - [no number] Engrave Trouble (Box 8)
    - [no number] Oscar's New Life (Box 8)
    - [no number] A Taste of Money (Box 8)
  - Ole Tourista
    - story proposal (Box 8)
  - One Day At a Time
    - 0323 Ann the Father (Box 8)
    - 0401 Father Dear Father part 1 (Box 8)